// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which Indian state/UT is to set up the country first Electric Vehicle park?",
    answer: "Tamil Nadu",
    options: [
      "Kerala",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Telangana",
      "karnataka"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "India is located on north of equator between which of the following latitudes?",
    answer: "Between 8°4 and 37°6",
    options: [
      "Between 8°4 and 37°6",
      "Between 7°4 to 39°6",
      "Between 8°7 to 36°6",
      "Between 7°4 to 40°6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which port is known as Queen of Arabian Sea?",
    answer: "Kochi Port",
    options: [
      "Vizag port",
      "Paradip port",
      "Kochi Port",
      "Mumbai Port"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Indravati Hydro Electric Project belongs to which state?",
    answer: "Orissa",
    options: [
      "Tamil nadu",
      "Orissa",
      "Karnataka",
      "Andhra Pradesh"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Through which of the following pass the river Satluj enters India from Tibet?",
    answer: "Shipki La",
    options: [
      "Nama pass",
      "Tanglang La",
      "Zojila",
      "Shipki La"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "At which among the following places, Brahamputra takes a U-turn at the time of entering into India?",
    answer: "Namcha Barwa",
    options: [
      "Kula Kangri",
      "Lunpo Gangri",
      "Namcha Barwa",
      "Noijin Kangsang"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The first factory by the Dutch was established at which among the following places?",
    answer: "Machilipatnam",
    options: [
      "Surat",
      "Machilipatnam",
      "Negapatnam",
      "Pulicat"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "At which of the following places held was held the All India Khilafat Conference in 1919?",
    answer: "Delhi",
    options: [
      "Mumbai",
      "Delhi",
      "Ahemdabad",
      "Pune"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Economic Planning comes under which of the following lists ?",
    answer: "Concurrent list",
    options: [
      "Union List",
      "Concurrent list",
      "State List",
      "None of them"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "World Economic Outlook is a survey conducted and published by the________?",
    answer: "International Monetary Fund",
    options: [
      "World Economic Forum",
      "World Bank",
      "World Trade Organization",
      "International Monetary Fund"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];